# **Hoppe Simon**

Email: hoppe.simon@outlook.com

## **Profile:**

Fullstack/Blockchain Engineer

I'm fullstack engineer who has over 10 year's experience in software development.

For a long time I worked in booking service platform including hotel, flight, car rental, transfer, attraction etc.

My strong skills are Golang, Node.js in backend, and React.js and Vuejs in frontend.

Recent I have several opportunities to work in blockchain world and implemented smart contracts and web3 products in evm, solana and flow blockchain.

I believe that my experience will have value in realizing the business needs of customers. I love to learn and strive to be faithful to my promises and responsibility.

Thanks.

## **Technical Skills:**

## **Backend/Frontend Oriented**

- Golang/Gin/Echo 6 years
- Node.js/Strapi 8 years
- Java/J2EE 6 years
- Php/Laravel 4 years
- Python/FastAPI 4 years
- React.js/React Native 6 years
- Vue.js 5 years
- Angular 1.x/2/5 3 years
- Elixir/Liveview 1 year

## **Blockchain Oriented**

- ERC-20, ERC-721, ERC-1155
- Solidity
- Rust
- Cadence
- Ethereum Blockchain
- Solana Blockchain

- Flow Blockchain

#### **Others**

- ibm cloud/AWS/Google cloud
- mysql/postgres/db2/mssql/oracle/mongodb
- docker/kubernates/Openshift/Jenkins/Gitlab CI
- firebase/kinvey
- Mqtt/Modbus/FIN/Opc-UA/HSMS etc

## **Qualifications:**

Bachelor Degree of Computer Science

## Languages:

English, Chinese, Polish

#### **Education:**

• 2006 - 2010 Bachelor Degree, Beijing Institute of Technology, Computer Science

## **Employment History:**

#### Smart Contract Developer, GigLabs, 2020.10 - 2022-12

- Developed GameFi smart contract on flow blockchain for Blocklete Golf Game Proshop(Cadence, Flow blockchain)
- Worked with backend part of GameFi(Node.js, postgres)
- Implemented EVM Smart contract and OpenBox from multiple NFTs(ERC 721, ERC 1155, Solidity, Hardhat), and Implemented dApp(React.js, web3)
- Implement NFTMarketplace on Ethereum
- Implement FlashLoan Bot on Ethereum
- Implement Game-Fi Smart Contract using Rust, Anchor on Solana

## Full stack/Blockchain Engineer, Bondly Finance, 2018.3 - 2020.8

- Improve feature of Crypto Wallet backend/front(Vue.js, Node.js, Cryptocurrency)
- Implemented new backend for Cryoto Wallet based on Golang(Golang)
- Implemented NFT raffle, Marketplace on Ethereum(Solidity)
- Implement swap dApp(Uniswap, web3)

# Full stack Engineer, FTI GmbH, 2014.1 - 2018.2

- Implemented Flight booking agency backend/frontend/admin panel(Golang, React.js, Postgres, Vue.js)

# Web Developer, DCC of China, 2010.6 - 2013.12

- Passed Java, SQL, Web courses
- Worked as web developer
- Maintenance ERP system